Guide to the Oswald G. Villard Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- G General, 1964-1975 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Gallagher Memorial Library Fund, 1961-1983 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1968-1970 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Bacon, Dr. D. C., 1964-1970 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Stanford University – Electrical Engineering Department PHD Qualifying Exams, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Performance Evaluation & Development Reviews, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- L general, 1965-1975 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Lasers, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Leadabrand material, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Lindau-Oblique Ionograms, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- M general, 1965-1982 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Mandelkern, David, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Marietta field site, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- 8812 project proposal, 1978-1984 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- 8812 project report file, general, 1979-1983 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- 8812 project monthly progress reports, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Harker, Ken memos, 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Robinson, L. A. RCS memos, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- DARPA proposal 634D83, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Masi, Joe, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- MEANS proposal, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Metal-Dielectric Discrimination IR&D, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Meteor Burst, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- METRRA (A. J. Behr), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Metze, George, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Miniature Wide Band Rotatable HF Directional Antenna, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- MITRE corporation, 1965-1970 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Mlodnosky, Robert Memorial Library Fund, 1963-1975 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Mode Averaging Diversity Combiner, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Moran, William J. Admiral, 1965-1978 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Moran, William J., consultant, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Morin, Armand, 1980-1983 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- MUSA antenna system, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- N general, 1967-1977 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- NAE (National Academy of Engineering), 1967-1972 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- NAE, 1968-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- NAE Electrical Engineering Communications/Computers/Control (Box 47, Folder 2)
- NAE meetings, 5/1973 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- NAE meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- NAE meetings, 1978-1983 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- NAS publications (Box 47, Folder 6)
- NAS, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- NAS, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- NAS, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- NAS, 1-6/1970 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- NAS, 7-12/1970 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- NAS, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- NAS Summer Study, 8-9/1971 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- NAS Committee on Undersea Warfare Panel on Countermeasures for Fleet Defense, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- NAS, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- NAS, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- NAS, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- NAS Panel of Reviewers, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- NAS, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- NAS, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- NAS, 1980-1983 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- NAS Day Projects Fund, 1969-1973 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- NRAC material, 1969-1976 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- NRAC lab binder, 1971-1975 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- NSAAB (National Security Agency Advisory Board) meeting, 12/4-5/1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- NSAAB meeting, 5/25-26/1985 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- NSAAB meeting, 3/13-14/1985 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- NSAAB member roster, 10/1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- NSAAB member roster, 3/1984 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- NSAAB correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- NSAAB findings, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- NCS Board of Visitors meetings, notes, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- NCS Board of Visitors, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- NCS Board of Visitors meeting, 9/17-18/1984 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- NCS Board of Visitors, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- NSAAB meeting, 3/13-14/1985 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- NSAAB facts & figures, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- NSAAB Innovative Technological Initiatives Ad Hoc group meeting, 1/27-28/1986 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- NSAAB meeting, 12/6/1985 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- NSAAB meeting, 9/16/1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- NSAAB 630D43-174, 9-10/1985 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- NSAAB 630D43-174, 11/1985 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- AFSB meeting, 5/9-11/1984 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- AFSB NAS travel, 1975-1983 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- AFSB correspondence, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- AFSB meeting, 9/22-23/1983 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- AFSB meeting, 7/26-27/1983 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- AFSB meeting, 10/12-13/1983 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- AFSB Advanced Airborne Surveillance Radar, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- AFSB meeting, 12/5-6/1979 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- AFSB meeting, 5/21-22/1979 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- AFSB, 1977-1979 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- NRAC meeting, 11/10-11/1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- NRAC meeting, 7/10-11/1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- NRAC meeting, 5/22-23/1975 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- NRAC meeting, 4/17-18/1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- NRAC correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- NRAC study on basic research, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- NRAC Hazen Report, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- NRAC meeting, 7/26/1974 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- NRAC meeting, 10/24-25/1974 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- NRAC meeting, 4/4-5/1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- NRAC meeting, 2/1-2/1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- NRAC Undersea Warfare/SCOE meeting, 6/5-7/1973 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- NRAC bulk data, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- NRAC correspondence, 7-12/1973 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- NRAC correspondence, 1-6/1973 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- NRAC meeting, 4/25-26/1974 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- NRAC meeting, 2/7-8/1974 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- NRAC meeting, 12/19-19/1973 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- NRAC Personnel Board meeting, 9/19/1973 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- NRAC newsletter, 9/1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- NRAC Laboratory Board meeting, 9/12/1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- NRAC meeting, 7/26-27/1973 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- ONR-64 (Office of Navy Research), 7-9/1970 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- ONR-64, 1-6/1970 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- ONR DARPA OHD meeting, 10/23-25/1968 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- ONR Coldspot project, 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- ONR contracts, 5-9/1967 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- ONR-64 general, 1966-1969 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- ONR-64 general, 1963-1965 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- ONR AF 33/657) 12901, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- ONR proposals, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- IEEE S. F. Fellow Committee, 1965-69 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Introductory talk on Radioscience Labs IDG (Box 55, Folder 5)
- International Conference on Communications, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- International Year of the Quiet Sun, 1962-1966 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- IR&D review, 11/1979 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- RCS IR&D briefing, 9/1978 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- IR&D review, 2/1976 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- IR&D reports, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- IR&D DSB Task Force, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- IR&D technical papers, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- DSB (Defense Science Board), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- American Geophysical Union, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- International Scientific Radio Union – paper abstracts, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- URSI (Union of Radio Science International) Nominating Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- URSI, 1971-1982 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- URSI meeting, 4/16-18/1970 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- URSI Nominating Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- National Bureau of Standards, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- National Medal of Science, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Naval Research Lab, 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- National Science Foundation, 1966-1974 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- National Security Planning Committee, 1977-1983 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- NSAC, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Navy RPV study, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- New corporation, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Newsclippings, 1967-1972 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- NSF proposals, 1971-1976 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- RSL staff, 1963-1970 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- NSF senior staff, 1964-1970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- S general, 1968-1983 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Document Accessions list, 1967-1968 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Security – Industrial Security Letters, 1965-1970 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Surveillance System Interaction Study, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Susskind, Charles, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- SWANN experiment, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Sylvania Electronics, 1965-1966 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- T general, 1965-1969 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- TAC (Technical Advisory Committee) meetings, 1965-1969 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- TACRAC I meeting, 2/17-19/1971 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- TAG (Technical Advisory Group) meeting, 6/10/1975 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- TAG, 5/1975 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- TEAL PARROT, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- TEAL PARROT, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- TEAL PARROT technical file, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- TEAL PARROT idea file, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Telegrams, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- TMC Research, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- TRW, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Transportable radar, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Tzedilina, Dr. E.E., 1975 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- News clippings (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Noise Canceling Receiver, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Non-linear Possibilities, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Non radiating Decoys for Anti-Radiation Missiles, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- NSG, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Naval Warfare Research Center bibliography, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- O general, 1966-1970 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Ocean Routes, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- RCS Suppression file, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Reprints Received, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Reeves Committee – aerospace, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Redwood Empire Telephone Company, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- RINT, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Roederer, Prof. Juan, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Rome Air Development Center, 1964-1970 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Rubenson, Joe (SRI Washington), 1972-1976 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Letters of Recommendation, 1971-1977 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Schischka, P.G. dissertation correspondence, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Science & Engineering Council in Support of the President, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Science & Government Report, 2/1/1973 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- SECEDE project, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- IDL Publication and Proposal Summaries, 1963-1979 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Rand Corporation, 1964-1966 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Stanford University Radioscience & Space Engineering Program brochure & material, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Ranger VIII moon pictures, 2/1965 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Ranger IX moon pictures, 3/1965 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Raytheon Company, 1964-1971 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- RCS administration & procedure memos, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- RCS measurements, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- URSI meeting, 9/9/1968 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- URSI meeting, 4/9-12/1968 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- URSI meeting engagements, 4/9-12/1968 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- URSI meeting correspondence, 4/9-12/1968 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- URSI meeting, 10/16-18/1967 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- URSI minutes of annual meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- USAF Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- US Army R & D group, 1964-1966 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Heynick, Lou memos, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Van Geen, John RCS memos, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Van Geen, John RCS memos, 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Harker, Ken CSI Theory memos, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- SARC (Stanford University Amateur Radio Club) directory, survey correspondence, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- SARC directory revisions, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Single Sideband AFC (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Single Sideband AFC (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Skane, William, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- SONOX, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Space Panel, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Stanford University Antenna, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- ERS Working Group for Planning, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- NRAC correspondence, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- NRAC meetings, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- NRAC correspondence, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- NRAC meetings, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- NRAC correspondence, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- NRAC bulk data, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- NRAC meetings, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- NRAC correspondence, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- NRAC bulk data, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- NRAC EAB (Exploitation Advisory Board) meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- ITEK Science Board, 1971-1973 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- NRAC-SCOE correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- NRAC-SCOE meetings, 1968-1971 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- NRAC-SCOE correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- NRAC correspondence, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- NRAC meeting, 10/23-25/1974 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- NRAC meeting, 7/25-26/1974 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- NRAC/DSB meetings, 4/14-19/1974 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- NRAC Lab Advisory Board, 1969-1974 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- NRAC nominations, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- NRAC C3 Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- NRAC, 1976-1978 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- NRAC review, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- NRAC EAB meeting, 6/7-8/1977 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- NRAC meeting, 2/16-17/1977 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- NRAC C3 meeting, 1/26-27/1977 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- NRAC Ad Hoc Committee on RPVs, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- NRAC newsletters, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- ITEK Science Board, 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- DARPA general correspondence, 1964-72 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- N00014-70-C-0413 Project files [ionospheric study], 9-12/1971 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- N00014-70-C-0413 Project files, 5-8/1971 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- N00014-70-C-0413 Project files, 9-12/1972 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- N00014-70-C-0413 Project files, 5-8/1972 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- N00014-70-C-0413 Project files, 1-4/1972 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Proposal material, 1-6/1969 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Proposal material, 6-8/1969 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Proposal requests, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Publications (Distribution Lists), 1971-1975 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Publications (External Requests for Technical Reports), 1970-1972 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Publications (Release of Technical Reports), 1970-1979 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Publications (Papers for Open Literature), 1965-1975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- B general BA-BN, 1964-1983 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- B general BO-BZ, 1965-1973 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Barry Research, Inc., 1969-1977 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Beacon Project Responses, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Berkner, Lloyd Memorial Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- BMEWS radar transmitter, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Stanford University - Committee on University Libraries, 1964-1965 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Stanford University - Committee on University Libraries, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Stanford University - Committee on University Libraries, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Stanford University - Committee on University Libraries Library Bulletin, 1965-1969 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Student Research Assignments (Graduate Assistants), 1964-1973 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- NAS reports, 1966-1977 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- NAS member rosters, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- NAS correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- NAS correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- NAS Committee meeting, 5/24-25/1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- NAS Membership Committee, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- National Research Council meeting, 11/2-4/1983 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Superior Electric Company, 1980-1982 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Superior Electric Company, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Superior Electric Company meeting, 7/29-31/1981 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Superior Electric Company project proposal, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Superior Electric Company memos, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Superior Electric Company literature, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Superior Electric Company transparencies, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Superior Electric Company, Peterson, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Superior Electric Company Miscellaneous reports, SRI Journal, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Superior Electric Company expense reports, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Superior Electric Company Board of Directors meeting, 11/11/1983 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Lusignan, Bruce, 1963-1966 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Manning, Lawrence, 1966-1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Mendelovicz, Ada, 1973-1976 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Rambo, W. R., 1964-1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Wedgwood, John W., 1966-1968 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Williams, Neal, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Annett, David M., 1965-1968 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Bly, Robert, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- RCS technical notes, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- RCS Spring Measurements, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- RCS Rainey Task 111, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- RCS 8361-10, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- RCS 8361-10, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- RCS William Scharfman, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- RCS Reduced Far Field Radiators, 1976-1979 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- RCS Suppression File, 1977-1979 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Reconix, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- McKinney, Dorothy, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Reyburn, Harold, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Rockwell, Mabel, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Schulz, Robert F., 1965-1966 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Schulz, Robert F., 1967 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Schulz, Robert F., 1968 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Schulz, Robert F., 1969 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- SRI salaries, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- SRI Villard travel expense reports, 1981-1983 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- SRI Villard travel expense reports, 1978-1981 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- SRI memos and correspondence, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- SRI memos and correspondence, 1-6/1971 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- SRI memos and correspondence, 7-12/1971 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- SRI Minority Employment Goals, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- SRI Presidential Prizes for Innovation, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Eshleman, Von, 1963-1970 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Ford, Ken, 1972-1976 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Garriott, Owen, 1963-1975 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Garriott Group, 1965-1968 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Goodman, Joseph, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Liston, Clive patents, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- NSAC presentations, 1987-1990 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous offprints, memos, reports, minutes (Box 72, Folder 2)
- SEL Instrument Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Stanford University - Committee on Service to Students, 1972-1973 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- IEEE Field Awards Committee, 1966-1972 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- IEEE Panel & meeting, 3/26/1966 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- IEEE S.F. Fellows Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- TAG meeting, 10/19/1976 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- TAG meeting, 5/25/1976 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Washington trip, 4/1976 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- TAG meeting, 5/8/1979 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Project files, 7-12/1974 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Project files, 1-6/1975 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Project files, 7-12/1975 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Project files, 1-6/1976 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Project files, 7-12/1978 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Project files, 1-6/1979 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Project files, 7-12/1979 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- SRI - ERS (Electronic & Radio Sciences Division), 1974-1978 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- SRI-ERS newsletter, 1975-1978 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- SRI Comparisons, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- SRI IR&D Program Prospectus, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- SRI memos general, 1964-1981 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- SRI memos & correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- NASA files, 1967-1968 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- NASA files, 1960-1960 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- NASA photographs, 1966 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- NASA publications, 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- 6390 Project Original Report Figures, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- 6390 Project, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- 6390 Project numbers, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- 6390 Project Research on Conformal Passive Devices, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- 7596 Project, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- 7839 Project, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- 7839 Project transparency, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- 1255 Project correspondence, 1984-87 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- 1255 Project European Briefing, 2/1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- 1255 Project VOA Draft Report, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- 1255 Project Progress Reports, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- 1255 Project URSI presentation, 1/1987 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- 1255 Project Design of Anti-Jamming Antennas, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- 1255 Project meeting, 9/1985 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- 1255 Project Idea File, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- 1255 Project Figures, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- 1255 Project VOA correspondence, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- 1255 Project meeting, 10/1985 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- 1255 Project meeting, 10/1985 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- 1255 Project meeting, 11/1985 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- 1255 Project Public Diplomacy Workshop, 10/3-4/1985 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- 1255 Project VOA proposal (Box 77, Folder 4)
- AFSC (U. S. Air Force Systems Command) meeting, 2/27-28/1968 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- AFSC meeting, 2/13/1969 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- AFSC, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- AFSC, 6-12/1973 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- AFSB (Air Force Studies Board) correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- AFSB meeting, 11/17/1977 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- AFSB study, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- AFSB meeting, 8/25-26/1982 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- AFSB meeting, 11/1-2/1982 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- AFSB meeting, 11/22-23/1982 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- AFSB meeting, 11/28-29/1984 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- PAVE PAWS report, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- PAVE PAWS references, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- PAVE PAWS correspondence1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- USAF-SAB (Scientific Advisory Board) Executive Committee meeting, 11/14/1967 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- USAF-SAB Executive Committee meeting, 4/16/1968 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- USAF-SAB Executive Committee meeting, 11/12/1968 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- USAF-SAB Executive Committee meeting, 11/4/1969 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- USAF-SAB Executive Committee meeting, 10/21/1970 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- USAF-SAB Executive Committee meeting, 4/6/1970 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- USAF-SAB reports, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- USAF-SAB meeting, 3/5/1968 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- USAF-SAB meeting, 3/1971 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- USAF-SAB Ad Hoc Committee in Ionospheric Research, 1968-1969 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- USAF-SAB report, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- USAF-SAB meeting, 5/4/1973 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- USAF-SAB meeting, 10/18-19/1973 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- USAF-SAB reports, 1973-1975 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- USAF-SAB Strategic Panel Meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- USAF-SAB Executive Committee meeting, 5/20/1974 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- USAF-SAB meeting, 5/21/1974 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- USAF-SAB meeting, 10/17-18/1974 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- USAF-SAB Cross Matrix Panel, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- USAF-SAB correspondence, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- USAF-SAB meeting, 1/24/1975 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- USAF-SAB Executive Committee meeting, 4/4/1975 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- URSI Inputs for Report to General Assembly, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- URSI correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- URSI member roster, 1967-1969 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- URSI agenda meeting, 4/21-24/1969 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- URSI/ARPA meetings, 12/8-12/1969 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- URSI Commission III correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- URSI International Office election, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- URSI general correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- URSI Booker Fellowship Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- URSI meeting, 9/14/1970 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- URSI meeting, 6/20-24/1977 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- URSI meeting, 7/1978 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- URSI U.S. Commission Executive Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- URSI meeting, 11/5-7/1979 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- URSI meeting, 1/6/1983 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- U general (Box 82, Folder 12)
- ULF Radar file, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- United Scientific Corp, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 14)